godeals.com 2019-06-26

# Brad's Deals Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our clients and partners. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our website (our "Site"), our mobile apps, our Amazon Alexa Skills, and our products and services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs. 

##  What Information Do We Collect? 

When you visit our Site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Site. 

### 1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide

If you choose to purchase products or services from our partners, you may need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following information: 

  * Name
  * Mailing address
  * Email address
  * Credit card number, expiration date and card verification number
  * Home and business phone number
  * Other personal information (i.e. mother's maiden name)
  * Email Information

In addition to providing the foregoing information to our partners, if you choose to correspond further with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone. 

### 2\. Site Use Information

Similar to other commercial web sites, our Site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Site, and the Sites visited just before and just after our Site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual. 

What Are Cookies? Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's Web browser on the user's hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized. 

## How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our traditional corporate standards designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our customers' personal information. As a customer, you will be given the opportunity, at least once annually, to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers. 

## How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?

We use Site browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather information about our Site users' browsing activities, in order to constantly improve our Site and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Site to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers. 

Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our Site as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our Site and evaluate our Site's visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture your individual email address or any personally identifying information about you although they do permit us to send focused online banner advertisements or other such responses to you. 

## How Do We Protect Your Information?

_Information Security._ We have implemented an information security program that contains administrative, technical and physical controls that are designed to reasonably safeguard personal information. We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration or destruction. 

_Evaluation of Information Protection Practices._ Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the security, confidentiality and quality of our information. 

_Employee Access, Training and Expectations._ Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes and transactions. 

## Communication Opt Out

If you wish to opt out of receiving offers directly from Brad's Deals LLC network or business partners, you can unsubscribe or follow the opt-out instructions in the emails that they send you located at the footer of the communication. 

## Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties?

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit both our Site and emails. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you on unaffiliated websites, apps, online service for advertising, analytics, attribution, reporting, and targeted emails based items viewed on a particular website. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) and Networking Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Site traffic patterns and related Site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data. Personally identifiable information will only be shared if the personally identifiable information has been freely given by the user to both Brad's Deals and the third party, and as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy. 

## What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. 

## What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information by us through your interaction with the Site. Other websites that may be accessible through links from the Site may have their own privacy policies and personal information collection, use, and disclosure practices. The merchants included on our Site (our "Business Partners") may also have their own privacy policies. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy policies provided by these other parties prior to providing them with information or taking advantage of a sponsored offer or promotion. 

Brad's Deals LLC has financial relationships with our Business Partners. Brad's Deals LLC may be compensated if consumers choose to apply for or purchase products or services via the links on our site. 

## Children's Privacy

The Site is a general audience site not directed at children under the age of 13. 

By using our Site, you represent that you are at least eighteen years old and understand that you must be at least eighteen years old in order to create an account and purchase the goods or services advertised through the Site. We will promptly delete information associated with any account we obtain actual knowledge is associated with a registered user who is not at least eighteen years old. 

## Social Networks

1\. Social Community Areas 

The Site may be accessible through or contain connections to areas where you may be able to publicly post information, communicate with others such as discussion boards or blogs, review products and merchants, and submit media content. Prior to posting in these areas, please read our Terms of Use carefully. All the information you post may be accessible to anyone with Internet access, and any personal information you include in your posting may be read, collected, and used by others. We recommend that you do not post any personal information in the social community areas. 

2\. Social Networks 

You may log in to the Site using certain social network credentials. To manage the sharing of certain personal information with us when you connect with us through social networking platforms or applications, refer to the privacy policy and settings of the social networking website or application. 

You also have the option to link social networks, such as Facebook, to your Brad's Deals account. Once you register with us and connect with the social network, you will be able to automatically post recent activity back to your social network. 

By proceeding through any of the above steps, you grant us permission to access all of the elements of your social network profile information that you have made available to be shared and to use it in accordance with the social network's terms of use and this Privacy Policy. 

## Contact Us; California Privacy Rights and Other Countries

Please contact us if you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, we can be reached by postal mail at 6115 Estate Smith Bay Suite 315 St. Thomas, VI 00802, or by phone at 877.970.0707. You can email us at suggestions@bradsdeals.com with questions, comments or suggestions. 

If you reside in Canada, you may have the right to be provided with access to personal information that we have collected about you and written information about our policies and practices with respect to the transfer of your personal information to vendors outside Canada. 

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California can obtain certain information about the types of personal information that companies with whom they have an established business relationship have shared with third parties for those third parties' direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. In particular, the law provides that companies must inform consumers about the categories of personal information that have been shared with third parties, the names and addresses of those third parties, and examples of the types of services or products marketed by those third parties. To request a copy of the information disclosure provided by us pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact us via the email or address stated above. Please allow 30 days for a response. 

If you are a California resident under the age of 18, and a registered user of any site where this policy is posted, California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits you to request and obtain removal of content or information you have publicly posted. To make such a request, please send an email with a detailed description of the specific content or information to suggestions@bradsdeals.com. Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you have posted and that there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal even if requested.
